[{"answer": " Hey, Sabrina.  How was your summer?  You look tan", "docId": "09-07", "aSentId": 12, "question": "", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " It was great.  I went to the beach for two weeks with my family and hung out a", "docId": "09-07", "aSentId": 13, "question": " Hey, Sabrina.  How was your summer?  You look tan", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " Thats cool.  Whered you go to the beach", "docId": "09-07", "aSentId": 17, "question": " It was great.  I went to the beach for two weeks with my family and hung out a", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " We went to Hawaii.  Have you ever been", "docId": "09-07", "aSentId": 18, "question": " Thats cool.  Whered you go to the beach", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " No, I havent", "docId": "09-07", "aSentId": 19, "question": " We went to Hawaii.  Have you ever been", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " This was my first time and it was so beautiful there", "docId": "09-07", "aSentId": 20, "question": " No, I havent", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " Thats what Ive heard.  What did you do while you were there", "docId": "09-07", "aSentId": 21, "question": " This was my first time and it was so beautiful there", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " My sister and I relaxed and laid out a lot.  We also went snorkeling and shel", "docId": "09-07", "aSentId": 22, "question": " Thats what Ive heard.  What did you do while you were there", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " Howd you like snorkeling?  That must have been cool", "docId": "09-07", "aSentId": 26, "question": " My sister and I relaxed and laid out a lot.  We also went snorkeling and shel", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " It was cool.  The water there is crystal clear and like glass.  You could se", "docId": "09-07", "aSentId": 30, "question": " Howd you like snorkeling?  That must have been cool", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " Whoa!  There were sharks in the water?  Werent you scared", "docId": "09-07", "aSentId": 34, "question": " It was cool.  The water there is crystal clear and like glass.  You could se", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " No.  They were just tiny ones.  Plus, they were the ones that dont bothe", "docId": "09-07", "aSentId": 35, "question": " Whoa!  There were sharks in the water?  Werent you scared", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " Oh, OK", "docId": "09-07", "aSentId": 39, "question": " No.  They were just tiny ones.  Plus, they were the ones that dont bothe", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " Yeah, trust me.  I would not have been in the water with big sharks!  Anyway", "docId": "09-07", "aSentId": 40, "question": " Oh, OK", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " Yeah.  My summer was good too.  I went to Canada with my friends for a wee", "docId": "09-07", "aSentId": 43, "question": " Yeah, trust me.  I would not have been in the water with big sharks!  Anyway", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " Thats neat.  Whyd you go to Canada", "docId": "09-07", "aSentId": 47, "question": " Yeah.  My summer was good too.  I went to Canada with my friends for a wee", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " Well, I cant stand the heat in the summer.  So, my friends and I decided to g", "docId": "09-07", "aSentId": 48, "question": " Thats neat.  Whyd you go to Canada", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " Oh, gotcha.  So what about the exchange student?  What was that like", "docId": "09-07", "aSentId": 52, "question": " Well, I cant stand the heat in the summer.  So, my friends and I decided to g", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " That was the best part of the summer, I think.  To be honest, I wasnt lookin", "docId": "09-07", "aSentId": 53, "question": " Oh, gotcha.  So what about the exchange student?  What was that like", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " Really?  What did they do while they were here", "docId": "09-07", "aSentId": 57, "question": " That was the best part of the summer, I think.  To be honest, I wasnt lookin", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": " He was just here to practice English and learn about American life.  So, h", "docId": "09-07", "aSentId": 58, "question": " Really?  What did they do while they were here", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " What did you do with him", "docId": "09-07", "aSentId": 62, "question": " He was just here to practice English and learn about American life.  So, h", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " I showed him around town.  We went to the movies, to the mall and out to lots o", "docId": "09-07", "aSentId": 63, "question": " What did you do with him", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " Really", "docId": "09-07", "aSentId": 67, "question": " I showed him around town.  We went to the movies, to the mall and out to lots o", "qSentId": 66},{"answer": " Yeah.  We went to the mountains and the beach for a weekend too so we coul", "docId": "09-07", "aSentId": 68, "question": " Really", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " That sounds pretty cool.  Did he teach you any Portuguese", "docId": "09-07", "aSentId": 72, "question": " Yeah.  We went to the mountains and the beach for a weekend too so we coul", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " Just a few words.  But, since he came here this summer, I get to go to Brazil nex", "docId": "09-07", "aSentId": 73, "question": " That sounds pretty cool.  Did he teach you any Portuguese", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " Thats awesome!  That sounds like a great program.  Id like to do that", "docId": "09-07", "aSentId": 79, "question": " Just a few words.  But, since he came here this summer, I get to go to Brazil nex", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " You should.  Its a really great way to learn about other countries and meet nic", "docId": "09-07", "aSentId": 80, "question": " Thats awesome!  That sounds like a great program.  Id like to do that", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " Yeah, maybe next summer I can host a student", "docId": "09-07", "aSentId": 84, "question": " You should.  Its a really great way to learn about other countries and meet nic", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " Ill give you the number of the exchange program office and you can tell the", "docId": "09-07", "aSentId": 85, "question": " Yeah, maybe next summer I can host a student", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " Thanks, John", "docId": "09-07", "aSentId": 89, "question": " Ill give you the number of the exchange program office and you can tell the", "qSentId": 88},{"answer": " No problem", "docId": "09-07", "aSentId": 90, "question": " Thanks, John", "qSentId": 89}]
